<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 15:21:54 +0700</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Get Started]]></title><url><![CDATA[get-started]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[Get Started]]></menu><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><content><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;col-12 col-md-12 p-3 p-md-5&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;shadow p-3 p-md-5 rounded&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Started work with get axcora cms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

				&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;After installation finish now you can accssess your website, visit /admin on your website then login using default data use username : axcora / password : axcoracms. and congratulations now you can accsess backend cms , and you need to change your password and title for Google SEO on setting fiturs.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;Click on settings and then change form with you needed, and save it.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upload File Media&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;For fast and easy for write a content post article you need upload all your media file like image and more , just click on file menu then you can create new folder with your own, and upload file in bottom menu . browse , select file and upload it.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Write Article Page and Post it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;After settings and upload all file is finish, now you can write a content and post for update or create new page on your website, just click on page menu then click new post and write your content. don&#039;t wory about SEO google features, because get axcora cms is automaticly generate your page title and description too.. all facebook or twitter tag is ready on use too. just focusing on your content then publish it. welcome to new CMS generation with using get axcora cms.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editing Home Page&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;By default the home page on welcome get axcora cms page, you can edited , just click on page and then edit title an content with you needed, you can upload image or link on your another page with click on text editor then select what you need.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Donation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;make a contribution by sharing our application with the world through your social media or voluntary donations to our account so we can give the best for you again.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;Donate Now using moneygram or western union.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;BANK CENTRAL ASIA&lt;br /&gt;
					ACCOUNT NO : 0181884109&lt;br /&gt;
					IBAN/SWIFT CODE : CENAIDJA&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private><author><![CDATA[axcora]]></author></item>
